Finding Aid for the John Phillip Hyatt Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Academic Career
  - Organizations
    - International Organization for the Study of the Old Testament (Box 27, File 7)
    - Jewish Palestine Exploration Society (Box 27, File 8)
    - Memphis Theological Seminary (Box 27, File 9)
    - National Association of Biblical Instructors (Box 27, File 10)
    - National Association of Professors of Hebrew (Box 27, File 11)
    - National Council on Religion in Higher Education (NCRHE)--Fellows Lists (Box 27, File 12-13)
    - NCRHE--Memoranda (Box 27, File 14)
    - NCRHE--Newsletters (Box 27, File 15-17)
    - NCRHE---Reports (Box 27, File 18)
    - NCRHE--Week of Work (Box 27, File 19-22)
  - Organizations
    - NCRHE--Miscellaneous (Box 28, File 1)
    - Rhodes University (Box 28, File 2)
    - Society of Biblical Literature (SBL) Annual Meetings--Paper Abstracts (Box 28, File 3-7)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Papers Presented, Notes, etc. (Box 28, File 8)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Proceedings (Box 28, File 9)
    - SBL--Annual Meetings--Programs (Box 28, File 10-11)
    - SBL--Council Meeting Papers (Box 28, File 12-13)
    - SBL--Membership Lists, etc. (Box 28, File 14)
    - SBL--Memoranda, etc. (Box 28, File 15)
    - SBL--Mid-West Section (Box 28, File 16)
    - SBL--Reports (Box 28, File 17)
    - SBL--Southern Section (Box 28, File 18)
    - SBL--Yonan Codex--Legal Papers, Notes (Box 28, File 19)
    - SBL--Yonan Codex--Memoranda (Box 28, File 20)
    - SBL--Yonan--Codex--Newspaper Clippings, Articles (Box 28, File 21)
  - Organizations
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Bulletins (Box 29, File 1)
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Meetings (Box 29, File 2)
    - Society for Old Testament Study--Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 3)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Bulletins (Box 29, File 4)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Lists, etc. (Box 29, File 5)
    - Yale Divinity School--Class Questionnaires (Box 29, File 6-8)
    - Yale Divinity School--Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 9-11)
    - Yale University--Newspaper Clippings (Box 29, File 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 29, File 13)
  - Events
    - Chicago School Congress (Vanderbilt Divinity School) (Box 29, File 14)
    - Congress of Religious Education in a New Age (Box 29, File 15)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Bibliography (Box 29, File 16)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Notes (Box 29, File 17)
    - Consultation on Hermeneutics--Papers (Box 29, File 18-21)
    - Consultation on the Teaching of the Biblical Languages (Box 29, File 22)
    - Interdenominational Ministries Institute (Box 29, File 23)
    - Seminar on Revelation as History (Box 29, File 24)
  - Church Activities
    - Disciples of Christ--Conventions (Box 30, File 1)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House-- Dean's Reports (Box 30, File 2-5)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Financial Reports (1951-66) (Box 30, File 6)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Financial Reports (1967-71) (Box 30, File 7)
    - Disciples of Christ--Disciples Divinity House--Miscellaneous (Box 30, File 8)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Constitution (Box 30, File 9)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Financial Reports (Box 30, File 10)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--The Harbinger (Box 30, File 11-12)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Memoranda (Box 30, File 13)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Meeting Agendas (Box 30, File 14)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society-- Meeting Minutes (Box 30, File 15-17)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Phillips Memorial (Box 30, File 18-19)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Planning Committee (Box 30, File 20)
  - Church Activities
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Press Releases (Box 31, File 1)
    - Disciples of Christ--Historical Society--Reports (Box 31, File 2-4)
    - Disciples of Christ -- Historical Society-- Miscellaneous (Box 31, File 5)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Memoranda (Box 31, File 6)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Minutes (Box 31, File 7)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Study Papers (Box 31, File 8-14)
    - Disciples of Christ--Panel of Scholars--Miscellaneous (Box 31, File 15)
    - Disciples of Christ--Woodmont Christian Church (Box 31, File 16)
    - Disciples of Christ--Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 31, File 17-18)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--Jewish Materials (Box 31, File 19)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--National Council of Churches (Box 31, File 20)
  - Church Activities
    - Ecumenical Concerns--Roman Catholicism (Box 32, File 1)
    - Ecumenical Concerns--World Council of Churches-- Faith and Order Commission (Box 32, File 2-4)
    - Preaching Engagements--Church Bulletins (Box 32, File 5-6)
- Community Activities
  - Community Relations Conference (Box 32, File 7)
  - South Street Center (Box 32, File 8)
  - Miscellaneous Materials on Race Relations (Box 32, File 9)
  - Various Social Issues (Box 32, File 10)
- Subject Files
  - Alcoholism (Box 33, File 1)
  - Ancient Near East--Assyriology (Box 33, File 2)
  - Ancient Near East--Canaanite Religion (Box 33, File 3)
  - Ancient Near East--Egyptology (Box 33, File 4-5)
  - Ancient Near East--Cyrus Gordon (Box 33, File 6)
  - Ancient Near East--Hittites (Box 33, File 7)
  - Ancient Near East--Mesopotamia (Box 33, File 8-10)
  - Ancient Near East--Palestine, Cultural History of (Box 33, File 11-14)
  - Ancient Near East--Ras Shamra (Box 33, File 15-16)
  - Archaeology--Articles (Box 33, File 17-18)
  - Archaeology--Lachish (Box 33, File 19)
  - Archaeology--Masada (Box 33, File 20)
  - Subject Files
    - Archaeology--North Semitic Epigraphy (Box 34, File 1-3)
    - Archaeology--Magazine Clippings (Box 34, File 4)
    - Archaeology--Newspaper Clippings (Box 34, File 5-6)
    - Archaeology--Notes (Box 34, File 7-11)
    - Archaeology--Palestine (Box 34, File 12)
    - Archaeology--Photographs (Box 34, File 13-15)
    - Archaeology--Wright, G. Ernest (Box 34, File 16)
    - Archaeology--Miscellaneous (Box 34, File 17)
    - Baptism (Box 34, File 18-19)
    - Baptist Polity and History (Box 34, File 20)
    - Alexander Campbell (Box 34, File 21)
  - Subject Files
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Bibliographies (Box 35, File 1)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Hodayot (Box 35, File 2)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Magazines, etc. (Box 35, File 3-5)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Magazine Clippings (Box 35, File 6)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Newspaper Clippings (Box 35, File 7)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Scholarly Papers and Arts. (Box 35, File 8-12)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Translations (Box 35, File 13-15)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--University of Wisconsin Radio Series (Box 35, File 16)
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Notes (Box 35, File 17-20)
  - Subject Files
    - Dead Sea Scrolls--Miscellaneous (Box 36, File 1)
    - History and the Historian (Box 36, File 2)
    - Indian Religion (Box 36, File 3)
    - Islam (Box 36, File 4)
    - Jerusalem (Box 36, File 5)
    - Judaism (Box 36, File 6-7)
    - Languages--Aramaic (Box 36, File 8-9)
    - Languages--Babylonian-Assyrian (Box 36, File 10-17)
    - Languages--Hebrew (Box 36, File 18-20)
    - Languages--Latin (Box 36, File 21)
    - Languages--Linguistics (Box 36, File 22)
  - Subject Files
    - Languages--Sumerian (Box 37, File 1)
    - Languages--Syriac (Box 37, File 2)
    - Languages--Ugaritic (Box 37, File 3)
    - Marxism (Box 37, File 4)
    - New Testament--Apocalyptic (Box 37, File 5)
    - New Testament--Gospel of John (Box 37, File 6)
    - New Testament--Jesus (Box 37, File 7-8)
    - New Testament--Miscellaneous (Box 37, File 9)
    - Old Testament--Ark and Ephod (Box 37, File 10)
    - Old Testament--Conquest (Box 37, File 11)
    - Old Testament--David (Box 37, File 12)
    - Old Testament--Dress (Box 37, File 13)
    - Old Testament--Love in Old Testament (Box 37, File 14)
    - Old Testament--Man in Old Testament (Box 37, File 15)
    - Old Testament--Messianism (Box 37, File 16)
    - Old Testament--Mosaic Faith (Box 37, File 17)
    - Old Testament--Myth in Old Testament (Box 37, File 18)
    - Old Testament--Pentateuch (Box 37, File 19-20)
    - Old Testament--Poetry (Box 37, File 21)
    - Old Testament--Prophecy (Box 37, File 22-24)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament--Salvation in Old Testament (Box 38, File 1)
    - Old Testament--Solomon (Box 38, File 2)
    - Old Testament--Text and Canon (Box 38, File 3-5)
    - Old Testament--Theology (Box 38, File 6-10)
    - Old Testament--Torah in Old Testament (Box 38, File 11)
    - Old Testament--Typology (Box 38, File 12)
    - Old Testament--Wisdom Literature (Box 38, File 13)
    - Old Testament--Yahweh (Box 38, File 14-16)
    - Old Testament Books--Genesis (Box 38, File 17-18)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament Books--Exodus--Notes (Box 39, File 1-2)
    - Old Testament Books--Exodus--Articles (Box 39, File 3-10)
    - Old Testament Books--Deuteronomy (Box 39, File 11)
    - Old Testament Books--Job (Box 39, File 12-15)
    - Old Testament Books--Psalms (Box 39, File 16-18)
  - Subject Files
    - Old Testament Books--Proverbs (Box 40, File 1)
    - Old Testament Books--Ecclesiastes (Box 40, File 2)
    - Old Testament Books--Isaiah (Box 40, File 3-4)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah (Box 40, File 5-9)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah 39:3 (Box 40, File 10)
    - Old Testament Books--Jeremiah--Repentance (Box 40, File 11)
    - Old Testament Books--Amos (Box 40, File 12)
    - Old Testament Books--Jonah (Box 40, File 13-14)
    - Old Testament Books--Micah (Box 40, File 15)
    - Old Testament Books--Habakkuk (Box 40, File 16)
    - Old Testament Books--Sirach (Box 40, File 17)
    - Old Testament Books--Wisdom of Solomon (Box 40, File 18)
    - Pastoral Counseling (Box 40, File 19)
    - Social Justice (Box 40, File 20)
    - Theology--Contemporary (Box 40, File 21)
    - Theology--Pannenberg--Bibliographies, etc (Box 40, File 22)
    - Theology--Pannenberg--Papers (Box 40, File 23-25)
    - Theology--Scriptural Authority (Box 40, File 26)
    - Vietnam (Box 40, File 27-28)
  - Personal
    - Oddities (Religious and Other) (Box 41, File 1)
    - Miscellaneous Pamphlets (Box 41, File 2)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Baylor University (Box 41, File 3)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Branscomb Distinguished Professor (Box 41, File 4)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--United Christian Missionary Society (Box 41, File 5)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Christian Theological Seminary (Box 41, File 6)
    - Awards, Honorary Degrees--Texas Christian University (Box 41, File 7)
    - Charitable Giving (Box 41, File 8)
    - Education Materials--University of Marburg (Box 41, File 9)
    - Education Materials--Yale Divinity School (Box 41, File 10)
    - Family--Elizabeth Bard Hyatt (Box 41, File 11)
    - Family--Lee Hyatt (Box 41, File 12)
    - Family--Robert Lee Hyatt--Cancelled Checks (Box 41, File 13)
    - Family--Robert Lee Hyatt--Legal Papers (Box 41, File 14)
    - Health Matters (Box 41, File 15)
    - High School Reunion (Box 41, File 16)
    - Legal Papers--Bradley Lumber Co. (Box 41, File 17)
    - Legal Papers--Insurance and Miscellaneous (Box 41, File 18)
    - Legal Papers--Union Bank and Trust (Box 41, File 19)
    - Legal Papers--War Manpower Commission (Box 41, File 20)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 41, File 21)
    - Photographs (Box 41, File 22)
    - Resumes, Vitae, etc. (Box 41, File 23)
    - Travel--Europe and Middle East (1931-32)--Diary (Box 41, File 24-25)
    - Travel--Geneva Trip (1965)--Receipts (Box 41, File 26)
    - Travel--Geneva Trip (1965)--Miscellaneous (Box 41, File 27)
    - Miscellaneous Personal Loose Calendar/Appointment Books--1951, 1952, 1954 (Box 41, File 28)
  - Personal and Writings by Others
    - Loose Calendar/Appointment Books—1955, 1956, 1956¬57, 1957-58, 1958-59, 1959-60, 1961, 1961-62, 1962¬63, 1963-64, 1964-65, 1965-66, 19666-67, 1967-68, 1968-69, 1969-70, 1970-71, 1971-72
  - Articles
    - Jeremiah 2-6 and Its Parallels (Box 4, File 1)
    - Jeremiah's Message for Today (August 1961) (Box 4, File 1)
    - Jeremiah's Message for Today (September 1961) (Box 4, File 1)
    - Joshua (Box 4, File 1)
    - Judges (Box 4, File 1)
    - Kings, I and II (Box 4, File 1)
    - Lessons From the Exile (Box 4, File 2)
    - Leviticus (Box 4, File 2)
    - Light from the Dead Sea (Box 4, File 2)
    - A Look at Twelve Books (Box 4, File 2)
    - Magic, Divination, and Sorcery (Box 4, File 2)
    - The Meaning of Suffering (Box 4, File 3)
    - The Meaning of the Scrolls (Box 4, File 3)
    - Meeting God Through Isaiah (Box 4, File 3)
    - The Message of the Seventh-Century Prophets for Today (Box 4, File 3)
    - The Messiah in Apocrypha and Pseudepigrapha (Box 4, File 3)
    - The Ministry of Scholarship (Box 4, File 3)
    - Moloch or Molech (Box 4, File 3)
    - Mordecai (Box 4, File 3)
    - Moses and the Ethical Decalogue (Box 4, File 3)
    - Nahum (Hastings Dictionary) (Box 4, File 4)
    - Nahum (Peake's Commentary) (Box 4, File 4)
    - A Nation's Decline and Downfall (Box 4, File 4)
    - Nehemiah (Box 4, File 4)
    - A Neo-Babylonian Parallel to Bethel-Sar-Eser, Zech. 7:2 (Box 4, File 4)
    - New Light on Nebuchadrezzer and Judean History (Box 4, File 4)
    - A New Look at the Dead Sea Scrolls (Box 4, File 4)
    - A Note on Yiwwada in Ps. 74:5 (Box 4, File 4)
    - Numbers (Box 4, File 4)
    - Obadiah (Annotated Bible) (Box 4, File 5)
    - The Old Testament Idea of God and Its Modern Relevance (Box 4, File 6)
    - The Old Testament View of Man (Box 4, File 6)
    - Old Testament Teaching About God's Discipline (Box 4, File 6)
    - On the Meaning and Origin of Micah 6:8 (Box 4, File 6)
    - The Origin and Meaning of Christian Baptism (Box 4, File 6)
    - The Origin of Mosaic Yahwism (Box 4, File 6)
    - The Original Text of Jeremiah 11:15-16 (Box 4, File 6)
    - The Peril From the North in Jeremiah (Box 4, File 7)
    - The Place of the Old Testament in the Christian Faith (Box 4, File 7)
    - Pre-Adamite (Box 4, File 7)
    - A Prophet Speaks to Our Day (Box 4, File 8)
    - Prophets of the Southern Kingdom (Box 4, File 8)
    - The Ras Shamra Discoveries and the Interpretation of the Old Testament (Box 4, File 9)
    - Reading the Bible Today (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Highroad, April 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Highroad. May 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Highroad, June 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Workers with Youth, April, 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Workers with Youth, May 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - Religion in the Old Testament (Workers with Youth, June 1948) (Box 4, File 9)
    - The Religion of the Old Testament (Box 4, File 10)
    - Responsible Under God (Box 4, File 10)
    - Resources for Use with Studies in Christian Living (Box 4, File 10)
    - The Revised Standard Version of the Bible (Box 4, File 10)
    - The Revised Standard Version (Box 4, File 10)
    - The Rise and Fall of a Nation (January 1949) (Box 4, File 11)
    - The Rise and Fall of a Nation (February 1949) (Box 4, File 11)
    - The Rise and Fall of a Nation (March 1949) (Box 4, File 11)
    - Road Map for the Book of Job (Box 4, File 11)
    - Ruth (Encyclopedia of Religion) (Box 4, File 11)
    - Ruth (Hastings Dictionary of the Bible) (Box 4, File 11)
    - "S" (Encyclopedia of Religion) (Box 4, File 12)
    - Samuel, I and II (Box 4, File 12)
    - Slave, Slavery (Box 4, File 12)
    - Smith, William Robertson (Box 4, File 12)
    - Solomon in All His Glory (Box 4, File 12)
    - The Sources of the Suffering Servant Idea (Box 4, File 12)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Aug. 13) (Box 4, File 13)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Aug. 22) (Box 4, File 13)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Aug. 29) (Box 4, File 13)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Sept. 5) (Box 4, File 14)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Sept. 12) (Box 4, File 14)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Sept. 19) (Box 4, File 14)
    - The Story of the English Bible (Sept. 26) (Box 4, File 14)
    - Support Bill S. 1161 (Box 4, File 14)
    - Textual Criticism of the Old Testament (Box 4, File 15)
    - This Bible Is for You (Box 4, File 15)
    - Torah in the Book of Jeremiah (Box 4, File 16)
    - The Translation and Meaning of Amos 5:23-24 Tribal God (Box 4, File 16)
    - Understanding the Psalms in the Revised Standard (Box 4, File 17)
    - Version Values In Reading Job (Box 4, File 17)
    - The View of Man in the Qumran "Hodayot" (Box 4, File 17)
    - Was There an Ancient Historical Credo in Israel and an Independent Sinai Tradition? (Box 4, File 18)
    - Was Yahweh Originally a Creator Deity? (Box 4, File 19)
  - Articles, Books (Box 5)
    - What Are the Dead Sea Scrolls? (Box 5, File 1)
    - The Writing of an Old Testament Book (Box 5, File 1)
    - Why Do the Innocent Suffer (Box 5, File 1)
    - Yahweh as "The God of My Father" (Box 5, File 2)
    - Yehezkel Kaufmann's View of the Religion of Israel Zephaniah (Box 5, File 2)
    - Untitled Sunday School Lesson (Box 5, File 2)
    - Miscellaneous Revisions for Articles (Box 5, File 3)
    - The Bible in Modern Scholarship (Draft) (Box 5, File 4)
  - Books
    - Exodus (Partial Draft) (Box 6, File 1)
    - Exodus (Complete Draft) (Box 6, File 2)
  - Books
    - A History of the Religion of Early Israel (Draft 1) (Box 7, File 1)
    - A History of the Religion of Early Israel (Draft 2) (Box 7, File 2)
    - A History of the Religion of Early Israel (Draft 3) (Box 7, File 3)
  - Books
    - The Heritage of Biblical Faith (Draft) (Box 8, File 1)
    - The Heritage of Biblical Faith (Proof) (Box 8, File 2)
    - Jeremiah: Prophet of Courage and. Hope (Box 8, File 3)
    - The Prophetic Criticism of Israelite Worship (Box 8, File 4)
    - The Treatment of Final Vowels in Early Neo-Babylonian (Box 8, File 5)
  - Book Reviews, Dissertation Bibliographies, Student Papers, Personal
    - Book Reviews: A - B (Box 9, File 1)
    - Book Reviews: C - G (Box 9, File 2)
    - Book Reviews: H - K (Box 9, File 3)
    - Book Reviews: L - N (Box 9, File 4)
    - Book Reviews: 0 - R (Box 9, File 5)
    - Book Reviews: S - W (Box 9, File 6)
    - Dissertation: Studies in Neo-Babylonian Documents (Box 9, File 7)
    - Student Papers: Confessio Fidei (Box 9, File 8)
    - Student Papers: Is There Empirical Proof of Life After Death (Box 9, File 9)
    - Student Papers: The Psychology of Sin (Box 9, File 10)
    - Student Papers: Religious Education in the Family (Box 9, File 11)
    - Student Papers: The Religious Significance of Higher and Historical Criticism (Box 9, File 12)
    - Student Papers: The Scriptures of the Religions (Box 9, File 13)
    - Student Papers: The Story of the Alphabet - A Study of Humanism (Box 9, File 14)
    - Student Papers: The Two Biblical Accounts of Creation (Box 9, File 15)
    - Personal Bibliographies (Box 9, File 16)
  - Sermons and Sunday School Lessons
    - The Abundant Life - The Approach of Morning (Box 10, File 1)
    - Backward or Forward - Brush Pile or Big Tree (Box 10, File 2)
    - The Call to Service - The Christ Who Would Not Compromise (Box 10, File 3)
    - The Christian and the Race Problem - Church Unity (Box 10, File 4)
    - Co-Workers With God - The Cure of Worry (Box 10, File 5)
    - Danger - Do "Hard Times" Mean Defeat? (Box 10, File 6)
    - The Empty Tomb and The Risen Lord - The Eternal God (Box 10, File 7)
    - The Face of Temptation - Fruit Bearing (Box 10, File 8)
    - A Future and a Hope—With God (Box 10, File 9)
    - The Gentle Cynic - The Guest of God (Box 10, File 10)
    - Handling Our Handicaps - Isaiah, Statesman—Prophet (Box 10, File 11)
    - Jesus and His Bible - Joshua the Leader (Box 10, File 12)
    - Labour Day Sermon - Loyalty (Box 10, File 13)
    - Making Decisions - The Mother of Jesus (Box 10, File 14)
    - The Necessity of Skepticism - Not By Bread Alone (Box 10, File 15)
    - Our Debt to Past and Future - Our Master Teacher (Box 10, File 16)
    - Palestine: Land of Contrasts - Place of the Old Testament in Christian Faith (Box 10, File 17)
    - A Plea for Cleansing - The Pursuing God of Love (Box 10, File 18)
    - Read It Through - The Roots of Democracy in the Old Testament (Box 10, File 19)
    - Sacred Correspondence - The Seventh Word (Box 10, File 20)
    - Shadows of Influence - The Sword and Peace (Box 10, File 21)
    - The Task Committed to the Disciples - Thinking Peace 2 3 This One Thing - The Two Stories (Box 10, File 22)
  - Sermons and Sunday School Lessons, Lectures and Speeches
    - Unanswered Prayer - What Is Man? (Box 11, File 1)
    - What Is Religion? - The Word of God (Box 11, File 2)
    - Untitled (Box 11, File 3)
    - Miscellaneous Notes (Box 11, File 4)
    - Prayers (Box 11, File 5)
    - Lectures and Speeches (Box 11, File 5)
    - Various Lectures on Archaeology (Box 11, File 6)
    - Austin, TX—Lectures given to Clergy Conference, June 6-7, 1955 (Box 11, File 7)
    - Little Rock, ARK—Lectures on history of Bible (Box 11, File 8)
    - Revised Standard Version—various addresses (1) (Box 11, File 9)
    - Revised Standard Version—various addresses (2) (Box 11, File 10)
    - Revised Standard Version—various addresses (3) (Box 11, File 11)
    - Union Theological Seminary—lectures on prophetic religion (Box 11, File 12)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 11, File 13)
  - Publishing Activities
    - Bethany Press (Box 12, File 1)
    - Books--Dialogue on Death (Box 12, File 2)
    - Books--Engnell Manuscript (Box 12, File 3)
    - Books--The Heritage of Biblical Faith--Business (Box 12, File 4)
    - Books--The Heritage of Biblical Faith--Promotional Material (Box 12, File 5)
    - Books--The Heritage of Biblical Faith--Reviews (Box 12, File 6)
    - Books--The Heritage of Biblical Faith--Miscellaneous (Box 12, File 7)
    - Books--Interpreter's One-Volume Commentary (Box 12, File 8)
    - Books--Jeremiah: Prophet of Courage and Hope--Reviews (Box 12, File 9)
    - Books--Jeremiah: Prophet of Courage and Hope--Miscellaneous (Box 12, File 10)
    - Books--May Festschrift (Box 12, File 11)
    - Books--New Century Bible--Exodus (Box 12, File 12)
    - Books--New Century Bible--Miscellaneous (Box 12, File 13)
    - Books--Peake's Commentary (Box 12, File 14)
    - Books--Prophetic Religion (Box 12, File 15)
    - Books--SBL--Business and Promotion (Box 12, File 16)
    - Books--SBL--Contributions--Conzelmann (Box 12, File 17)
    - Books--SBL--Contributions--Robinson (Box 12, File 18)
    - Books--SBL--Contributions--Miscellaneous (Box 12, File 19)
    - Books--SBL--Contributors (Box 12, File 20)
  - Publishing Activities
    - Books--SBL--Galleys (Box 13, File 1)
    - Books--SBL--Reviews (Box 13, File 2-3)
    - Books--SBL--Miscellaneous (Box 13, File 4)
    - Books--Smith-Goodspeed Annotated Bible--Articles (Box 13, File 5)
    - Books--Smith-Goodspeed Annotated Bible--Miscellaneous (Box 13, File 6)
    - Books--Trantham Memorial Volume (Box 13, File 7)
    - Books--Treatment of Final Vowels in Early Neo-Babylonian (Box 13, File 8)
    - Books--Universal Bible Project (Box 13, File 9)
    - Encyclopedias and Dictionaries--Encyclopedia Americana (Box 13, File 10)
    - Encyclopedias and Dictionaries--Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 13, File 11)
    - Encyclopedias and Dictionaries--Harper's Dictionary of Biblical Biography (Box 13, File 12)
    - Encyclopedias and Dictionaries--Hasting's One-Volume Dictionary of the Bible (Box 13, File 13)
    - Encyclopedias and Dictionaries--Interpreter's Dictionary (Box 13, File 14)
    - Journals--Interpretation (Box 13, File 15)
    - Journals--Journal of Biblical Literature (Box 13, File 16)